SPOOKY IN LOVE
EPISODE 7
INCOMING CALL
DIRECTOR OF YEEON
PERSONAL INFORMATION REPORT
SUBJECT: MA GANG-UK
DETAILS, HEART TRANSPLANT SURGERY /
DAEHAN JUNGANG HOSPITAL
INCOMING CALL
PROSECUTOR MA
GOOD LUCK ARCADE
PLEASE TAP YOUR CARD ON THE SCREEN
1,000 WON APPROVED
NAVIGATION
NUNNOPPI BRIDGE, GIMPO HANGANG RIVER HIVE
REPORT, 2016-2026
ACQUISITIONS AND TRANSACTION RECORD
OF ARTWORK PLACED IN HOTELS
APPLICANT
DEBTOR: CHEON DONG-JUN
INCOMING CALL
CEO CHEON YEO-RI
CALLING…
DISTRICT CHIEF PROSECUTOR
CIVIL SERVANT PERSONNEL RECORD
NAME (KOREAN): MA GANG-UK
SEOUL CENTRAL DISTRICT PROSECUTOR'S OFFICE
INCOMING CALL
REINA CEO CHEON YEO-RI
WITNESS INFORMATION:
KANG MIN-HWAN (MALE, 22)
INITIAL REPORT: ON-SITE SAFETY MANAGEMENT
OFFICER (KIM TAEK-GEUN) TO CITY/PROVINCE
SECOND REPORT: SITUATION ROOM OFFICER
(PARK SEONG-HWAN) TO CITY/PROVINCE
THIRD REPORT: SITUATION ROOM OFFICER
(JEON JEONG-GUK) TO PUBLIC SAFETY MINISTRY
MALE (B) SPOTTED TWO PEOPLE, REPORTED IT,
AND EMTS WERE DISPATCHED TO THE SCENE,
THE TWO DROWNING VICTIMS WERE RESCUED
AND FIRST AID WAS PROVIDED,
BUT MALE (A) DIED AT THE SCENE,
WHILE FEMALE (E) REGAINED CONSCIOUSNESS
AND WAS TRANSPORTED TO THE HOSPITAL
BODY OF MS. JANG, PRO GOLFER
PARK SEUNG-JAE'S EX-GIRLFRIEND, FOUND
PARK SEUNG-JAE WANTED BY POLICE
AS PRIME SUSPECT
SPOOKY IN LOVE